Jenny: Hello?
Rob: Hello. Is that, uh, Jennifer Zielinski?
Jenny: Yes. Who’s that?
Rob: This is Rob Walker.
Jenny: I’m sorry, who?
Rob: Rob Walker. I work for London 24seven.
We need to talk about your trip to London in March.
Er, you arrive on the 12th of March and
you leave on the 19th, is that right?
Jenny: I’m really sorry Mr. Walker…er, Rob,
but I’m not at work.
Today is a holiday here.
Rob: A holiday?
Jenny: Yes, you know, it’s Thanksgiving.
I’m at my parent’s house, with my family.
Rob: Thanksgiving. Of course.
Sorry.
We don’t have Thanksgiving in England.
Jenny: No problem.
Listen, call me on Monday at work.
No, not Monday, Tuesday.
Rob: Tuesday the third of December?
Jenny: Yes.
Jenny’s mom: Jenny! Hurry up!
Jenny: Talk to you on Tuesday.
Thanks for calling.
Rob: Bye.
Jenny: Bye.